Guide to the Kristine Stiles Collection, 1900-[ongoing] RL.01254
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Name files, 42 boxes
  - Kelly, Caitlin Margaret, 2014 and undated (Box 212)
  - Kelly, Eileen (Box 149)
  - Roms, Heike, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Kelly, Gemey, Owens Art Galler, Mount Allison University, 1998-2001 (Box 149)
  - Kenny, Morgan, 2005 (Box 149)
  - Kentridge, William, 2001 (Box 149)
  - Keohane, Nannerl, 2000 (Box 149)
  - Khanna, Ranjana, 2005-2006 (Box 149)
  - Kiefer, Anselm (Box 149)
  - Kiganda, Julian, 2007 (Box 149)
  - Kirby, Peter, 1998 (Box 149)
  - Kim, Alice (Box 214)
  - Kirchwehm, Ward, 1994 (Box 149)
  - Kirshman, Deborah, 1998-2006 (Box 149)
  - Kivlan, Anna, 2008 (Box 149)
  - Klakuke, Jürgen, 1998 (Box 149)
  - Klein, Yves, 1993 (Box 149)
  - Klocker, Hubert, 2002 (Box 149)
  - Klopfer, Peter and Martha, 2004-2005 (Box 149)
  - Knowles, Alison, 1993-2007 (Box 149)
  - Kohn, Michael, 1998 (Box 149)
  - Kommunikationsguerilla-Wlet-Tournee, 1997 (Box 149)
  - Konhaus, Frank, 2010 (Box 149)
  - Koonz, Claudia, 1997-2006 (Box 149)
  - Koppelkamm, Stefan, 1983-1986 (Box 149)
  - Kos, Paul, 1998 (Box 149)
  - Kossuth, Louis (Box 149)
  - Kostabi, Mark, 1991 (Box 149)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1978-1993 (Box 149)
  - Kotz, Liz, 1992 (Box 149)
  - Kouneva, Penka, 1992-2001 (Box 149)
  - Kozelj, Marinela, 2000 (Box 149)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, 1994-1997 (Box 149)
  - Krajewski, Piotr, 1998 (Box 149)
  - Krash, Joan, 1988 (Box 149)
  - Kren, Kurt, 1967-1968 (Box 149)
  - Kretsinger, Robert, 2004-2006 (Box 149)
  - Kremen, Irwin, 1981-2007 (Box 150)
  - Krüppelschlang, 1999 (Box 150)
  - Krystufek, Elke, 2002-2008 (Box 150)
  - Kryzewski, Mike 2004 (Box 150)
  - Kukac #2, July 1991 (Box 150)
  - Kuklinski, Alyce, 2011 (Box 150)
  - Kultermann, Udo, 1984-1988 (Box 150)
  - Kultur Kontakt (Box 150)
  - Kunsthiorisch Institute (Box 150)
  - Kunstmuseum Wolfsburg, Young British Art exhibit poster, 1996 (Box 150)
  - Kurte, Stephen (Box 214)
  - Kushnick, Hannah, 2006 (Box 150)
  - Kyle, Elizabeth, 1999-2001 (Box 150)
  - La Frenais, Rob, 1995 (Box 150)
  - Labalme, Jenny, 1987 (Box 150)
  - Lacoste, Jean-Yves (Box 150)
  - Lacy, Suzanne, 1992-2003 (Box 150)
  - Lamb, Michael, 1992 (Box 150)
  - Lambert, Lee, 2010-2011 (Box 150)
  - Lange, Peter, 2000-2014 (Box 150)
  - Langenbach, Ray, 1997-2000 (Box 150)
  - Lasch, Peter (Pedro), 2003-2009 (Box 150)
  - Lauf, Cornelia, 1994-2000 (Box 150)
  - Lauridsen, Hanne, 1986-1994 (Box 150)
  - Laurie, Jean (Box 150)
  - Lavin, Maud, 1998-2007 (Box 150)
  - Lawrence, Bruce, 1995-2009 (Box 150)
  - Lawrence, Sidney, 1985-1992 (Box 150)
  - Layzell, Richard, 1979-1997 (Box 151)
  - Lê, Dinh Q. (Box 151)
  - Le Lann, Gerard (Box 151)
  - Leary, Robyn, 1987 (Box 151)
  - Lebel, Jean-Jacques, 2003 (Box 151)
  - Lebow, Ali (Box 214)
  - Lee, Pamela, 2009 (Box 151)
  - Lee, Thomas, 1990-2005 (Box 151)
  - Lee, Young Ji (Box 151, Box 214)
  - Leighten, Patricia, 1997-2005 (Box 151)
  - Lennox, Lillian, 1993 (Box 151)
  - Lenoir, Tim, 2008-2009 (Box 151)
  - Lentz, Elizabeth Anne, 2003 (Box 151)
  - Leonard, Shirley, 1995 (Box 151)
  - Lerager, James, 1994-2008 (Box 151)
  - Lerner, Jeff, 1993 (Box 151)
  - Lesnewski, Christopher, 1986-1998 (Box 151)
  - Levitz, Tamara, 2001 (Box 151)
  - Levy, Ellen (Box 151)
  - Lewallen, Constance, 2008 (Box 151)
  - Lewenz, Elisabeth, 2002 (Box 151)
  - Lewis, Sarah, 2006 (Box 151)
  - Libaw, William, 2003 (Box 151)
  - Libera, Zbignew, 1998 (Box 151)
  - Lierse, Henning, 1996-1998 (Box 151)
  - Liftman-Cohen, Ariane (Box 151)
  - Lifton, Robert (Box 151)
  - Lignon, Glenn (Box 151)
  - Lindsey, Susan A. K., 1996 (Box 151)
  - Lippard, Lucy, 2000 (Box 151)
  - Lipton, Quinn (Box 151)
  - Little, David, 1995-2007 (Box 152)
  - Locus+ Publishing (Box 214)
  - Loeffler, Carl (Box 152)
  - Logan, Juan (Box 152)
  - Long, Bert, 1993 (Box 152)
  - Longhauser, Elsa, 1998-2000 (Box 152)
  - Lotringer, Sylvere, 2003-2005 (Box 152)
  - Lovejoy, Margo, 1995-2006 (Box 152)
  - Lubell, Bernard, 1984 (Box 152)
  - Lubowsky, Susan (Box 152)
  - Lucero, Michael, 1997 (Box 152)
  - Lukens, Alan W., 2012 (Box 152)
  - Lupa?, Anna (Box 152)
  - Lure (Box 152)
  - Lüscher, Ingebard, 1995 (Box 152)
  - Ly, Boreth, 2009 (Box 152)
  - Lyles, Cosmos, 2002 (Box 152)
  - Macari, Lucia, 2002 (Box 152)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1998 (Box 152)
  - MacBeth, George, 1985 (Box 152)
  - MacDonald, Kevin, 1998 (Box 152)
  - Maciunas, Billie, 2008-2010 (Box 152)
  - Macke, Mirek, 1999 (Box 152)
  - Maertz, Gregory, 2009 (Box 152)
  - Mai, Hoáng Nuh (Box 152)
  - Mailloux, Suzanne, 1980-2000 (Box 152)
  - Majewski, Lech, 1992-2006 (Box 152)
  - Makhijani, Arjun, 1994-2006 (Box 152)
  - Malen, Lenore, 2002-2006 (Box 152)
  - Malloy, Vanja, 2011-2015 (Box 152, Box 214)
  - Malone, Michael, 2007 (Box 152)
  - Malpass, Gillian, 2000 (Box 152)
  - Manca, Ioana-Magdalena, 1996 (Box 152)
  - Mandel, Jay, 1994 (Box 152)
  - Manea, Ioana, 1993 (Box 153)
  - Manifesta, 1996-2000 (Box 153)
  - Manley, Roger, 1992-2005 (Box 153)
  - Mann, Tamara, 2001-2003 (Box 153)
  - Mannewitz, Peter, 1997 (Box 153)
  - Manovich, Lev, 2007 (Box 153)
  - Mansback, Steven, 2004 (Box 153)
  - Maravell, Zinnia, 1987 (Box 153)
  - Marchetti, Walter, 1999 (Box 153)
  - Marclay, Christian, 2000 (Box 153)
  - Maria, Diana and Carmen Savu (Box 153)
  - Marinela, Rasa, 2002 (Box 153)
  - Marioni, Tom, 1979-2010 (Box 153)
  - Maroja, Camilla, 2009 (Box 153)
  - Marranca, Bonnie, 1994-2008 (Box 153)
  - Martel, Richard, 1998-1999 (Box 153)
  - Martin, Henry, 2002 (Box 153)
  - Mathaf: Arab Museum of Modern Art, Doha, Qatar, 2010 (Box 153)
  - Mathery, Lynn, 1997-2000 (Box 153)
  - Mathieu, Georges, 2002 (Box 153)
  - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 2000-2002 (Box 153)
  - Matuso (Box 153)
  - Maurice, Emmanuel, 1974-1979 (Box 153)
  - Mausbach, Steven, 2011 (Box 153)
  - Mavor, Carol, 2000-2002 (Box 153)
  - May, Joshn, 1995-1997 (Box 153)
  - May, Nancy Tuttle, 1998 (Box 153)
  - Maybank, Tom (Box 153)
  - McAuliffe, Jody, 2008 (Box 153)
  - McBride, Kerry, 2010 (Box 153)
  - McCarthy, David, 2000 (Box 153)
  - McClain, Jain (Box 153)
  - McCoy, Ann, 1998-2003 (Box 153)
  - McDarrah, Fred, 2001 (Box 153)
  - McEvilley, Thomas, 2008 (Box 153)
  - McFadden, Jane and Patrick Lakey, 2006 (Box 153)
  - McFarlane, Harriet, 1994 (Box 153)
  - McGrath, Frank (Box 153)
  - McLendon, George, 2006-2009 (Box 153)
  - Mead Art Museum, Amherst College, 2003 (Box 153)
  - Medalla, David (Box 153)
  - Mehralian, Anne Marie and Mahmoud, 2003 (Box 153)
  - Melchert, Jim, 1985-2005 (Box 153)
  - Memo, Carl, 2000-2002 (Box 154)
  - Mendelsohn, Lousie, 1978 (Box 154)
  - Mendieta, Ana, 1997 (Box 154)
  - Meredith, Jill, 1999-2006 (Box 154)
  - Meta-Bauer, Uta, 1997-2004 (Box 154)
  - Metzel, Luise, 1996 (Box 154)
  - Metzger, Gustav (Box 154)
  - Meyers, Carol, 1986 (Box 154)
  - Meyers, Steve, 1975 (Box 154)
  - Mezzatesta, Michael, 1997 (Box 154)
  - Midori (Box 154)
  - Mih?lia, Rodica, 1994 (Box 154)
  - Mihaltianu, Dan, 1996-1997 (Box 154)
  - Mikacich, Jane, 1983 (Box 154)
  - Milkos, Erdely (Box 154)
  - Miller, Larry, 1999-2010 (Box 154)
  - Miller, Lauren (Box 154)
  - Millett, Kate, 1997 (Box 154)
  - Miloux, Yaunick (Box 154)
  - Min, Yong Soon, 2000-2008 (Box 154)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Art, 2009 (Box 154)
  - Mintz, Tommy, 2010 (Box 154)
  - Mircea, Florian and Gabriel Tomescu (Box 154)
  - Miscellaneous Contacts (Box 154)
  - Mitchell, W. J. T., 2000-2002 (Box 154)
  - Mitelman, Allan, 1978-2009 (2 folders) (Box 154)
  - Mitooka, Eiji, 2012 (Box 155)
  - Moisescu, Mihaela (Box 155)
  - Moldovan, Cosmin, 2005 (Box 155)
  - Mollison, James (Box 155)
  - Monk, Meredith, 2008 (Box 155)
  - Montano, Linda, 1984-2008 (Box 155)
  - Mooney, Jane, 1992 (Box 155)
  - Moore, Barbara, 1992-1996 (Box 155)
  - Moore, Peter, 1998-2000 (Box 155)
  - Moore, Robin (Box 155)
  - Moore, Steven, 1981 (Box 155)
  - Moorman, Charlotte, 2000 (Box 155)
  - Moran, George (Box 155)
  - Moran, Mailande, 2005-2006 (Box 155)
  - Morelli, Patrick (Box 155)
  - Morgan, David, 2008 (Box 155)
  - Morgan, Robert C., 1993 (Box 155)
  - Mori, Mariko, 1999 (Box 155)
  - Morris, Catherine, 2001 (Box 155)
  - Moss, Karen, 1997-1999 (Box 155)
  - Mottahedeh, Neger, 2005-2009 (Box 155)
  - Mühl, Otto (Box 155)
  - Mullican, Matt, 2001 (Box 155)
  - Munk, Annette, 1999 (Box 155)
  - Munroe, Alexandra, 2005-2008 (Box 155)
  - Muntandas, Antonio, 1994-2004 (Box 155)
  - Murakami, Takashi, 1999 (Box 155)
  - Murashige, Stanley, 1998 (Box 155)
  - Murphy, Mark, 2003-1993 (Box 155)
  - Murphy, Michael, 2007-2008 (Box 155)
  - Murphy, Timothy, 2007-2008 (Box 155)
  - Murphy, William, 1999 (Box 155)
  - Murray, Robert, 1997 (Box 155)
  - Murray-Wassnick, Sands, 2006 (Box 155)
  - Muesum of Modern Art, New York, 2010 (Box 155)
  - Musgrave, Victor, 1982 (Box 156)
  - Nagy, Rebecca (Box 156)
  - Naimark, Michael, 2007 (Box 156)
  - Nasher Museum of Art, gifts made by Stiles to, 2012 (Box 156)
  - Natale, Michele, 2007 (Box 156)
  - Nathans, Sydney, 2006 (Box 156)
  - National Museum of Contemporary Art, Bucharest, Romania (Box 156)
  - Nasher, Nancy, 2013 (Box 214)
  - National Coalition to Save Our Mall, 2001 (Box 214)
  - Naylor, Thomas, 2006 (Box 156)
  - Neagu, Paul, 1996 (Box 156)
  - Neblett, Leslie, 1994 (Box 156)
  - Nechvatal, Joseph, 2004 (Box 156)
  - Necro Enema Amalgamated (Box 156)
  - Nesbit, Molly (Box 156)
  - Neshat, Shirin, 2008 (Box 156)
  - Neuer Berliner Kunstverein (n.b.k.), 2011-2013 (Box 156, Box 214)
  - New, Jennifer, McCracken, 1997 (Box 156)
  - Newman, Bob, 1984 (Box 156)
  - Nicholson, Gerhard, 1995 (Box 156)
  - Nicolaescu, Madalina, 1996 (Box 156)
  - Nicolescu, Adrian, 1994 (Box 156)
  - Nihilist Industries (Elisha Shapiro), 1997 (Box 156)
  - Nilsson, John Peter, 1999 (Box 156)
  - Ninio, Moshe, 1995 (Box 156)
  - Nir + Erez (Box 156)
  - Nitsch, Herman, 1999-2011 (Box 156)
  - Nitoslawska, Marielle, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Nitsch, Hermann - Stiles's notes on attentnding Nitsch's "6 Day Play," August, 1998 (Box 156)
  - Nochlin, Linda (Box 156)
  - Pavelich, David (Duke University Libraries) (Box 214)
  - Noel Gallery (Box 156)
  - Nicholson, David, 1986 (Box 214)
  - Noh, Jiyang, 2000 (Box 156)
  - Noland, William, 1995-2009 (Box 156)
  - Norman, Sally Jane, 2006 (Box 156)
  - North Carolina-Israel Partnership, 1998 (Box 156)
  - Norton, Scott, 1994 (Box 156)
  - Noto, Katie (Box 156)
  - Novakov, Anna and Rik Richey (Box 156)
  - November, Winter 2006 (Box 156)
  - Obadike, Keith and Mendi Lewis (Box 156)
  - O'Dell, Kathy, 1979-2005 (Box 157)
  - O'Dell, Kathy, 1979-2005 (Box 157)
  - Odita, Odili Donald, 2008 (Box 157)
  - O'Grady, Lorraine, 1998 (Box 157)
  - Oguibe, Olu, 2007 (Box 157)
  - O'Hagan, Michael (Box 157)
  - O'Hara, Morgan, 1980-2001 (Box 157)
  - Okamuka, Keiko, 1998 (Box 157)
  - O'Keefe, Georgia, 1955 (Box 157)
  - Olin, Robert, 2003 (Box 157)
  - Oliveira, Nathan, 1983 (Box 157)
  - Olson, Adrian, 1993 (Box 157)
  - Taipei Fine Arts Museum, 1999 (Box 214)
  - Ono, Yoko, 1982-2009 (Box 157)
  - O'Neill, Lidia Falcón (Box 157)
  - Onslow-Ford, Gordon (Box 158)
  - Opie, Catherine, 2007 (Box 158)
  - Oppenheim, David, 1993-2006 (Box 158)
  - Opperman, Anna, 1989 (Box 158)
  - Orgeron, Marsha, 2007-2008 (Box 158)
  - ORLAN (Box 158)
  - Ortiz, Raphael Montañez, 1985-1994 (Box 158)
  - Osaki, Shinichiro, 1995-1998 (Box 158)
  - Osmund, Alex, 2007 (Box 158)
  - Oteri, Giacomo, 2000 (Box 158)
  - Ott, Sabina, 1986-2004 (Box 158)
  - Oursler, Tony, 1997 (Box 158)
  - Out of Actions, Museum of Contemporary Art, 1998 (Box 158)
  - Pace, Sean (Box 158)
  - Pacheles, Rodrigo Pachelis Nuñez, 2004 (Box 158)
  - Packer, Randall, 2001 (Box 158)
  - Pagani, Jacqualine, 1996 (Box 158)
  - Page, David A., 1990-1993 (Box 158)
  - Page, Robin, 1982 (Box 158)
  - Page, Susan Harbage, 2003 (Box 158)
  - Paik, Nam June, 1995 (Box 158)
  - Paiz, Fernando, 1999 (Box 158)
  - Palestine, Charlemagne, 2006-2008 (Box 158)
  - Paletz, David L., 1989-1993 (Box 159)
  - Panafieu, Christine de, 1982-1983 (Box 159)
  - Paris, Jan, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Papworth, John (Rev.) (Box 159)
  - Parallax (Box 159)
  - Pardo, Jorge, 1997 (Box 159)
  - Park, Andrus, 1993 (Box 159)
  - Paschall, John, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Parr, Kelly (Box 159)
  - Parr, Mike (Box 159)
  - Pasat, Alexandru (Box 159)
  - Paschal, Huston, 1993-2009 (Box 159)
  - Patterson, Ben, 2000 (Box 159)
  - Pau, Livinia (Box 159)
  - Pauline, Mark (Box 159)
  - Paulos, Eric, 1999 (Box 159)
  - Pauwels, Jon, 2001 (Box 159)
  - Payne, Bruce, 1999 (Box 159)
  - Peacock, Jan, 1981 (Box 159)
  - Pejic, Bojana, 1999-2009 (Box 159)
  - Penn State, Performance Art, Culture, and Pedagogy Symposium, 1996 (Box 159)
  - Perchuk, Andrew, 2005 (Box 159)
  - Pérennès, Marc, 2005 (Box 159)
  - Pérez, Virginia, 2008 (Box 159)
  - Periferic #2, Matei Bejanaru, 1998 (Box 159)
  - Perlman, Hirsch, 2004 (Box 159)
  - Perloff, Marjorie, 2001 (Box 159)
  - Perloff, Nancy, 2001 (Box 159)
  - Perriquett, Olivier, 2008 (Box 159)
  - Perry, Gill, 2003 (Box 159)
  - Person, Leroy, 2000 (Box 159)
  - Pervolovic, Romelo, 1996 (Box 159)
  - Pes, Luca, 2006 (Box 159)
  - Peters, Sharon, 2002 (Box 159)
  - Petersen, Stephen, 2006 (Box 159)
  - Pflaume, David, 1983 (Box 159)
  - Phelan, Peggy, 1998-2010 (Box 159)
  - Phillips, Lisa, 1998 (Box 159)
  - Phillips, Morgan, 2008 (Box 159)
  - Phillpot, Clive, 1994-2007 (Box 159)
  - Picard, Lil, 1981-1982 (Box 160)
  - Picard, Lil, 1982 (Box 160)
  - Picasso, 1997 (Box 160)
  - Piene, Otto, 2002 (Box 160)
  - Pierce-Baker, Charlotte, 2006 (Box 160)
  - Pindell, Howardena, 2006 (Box 160)
  - Pinkel, Sheila, 1993-2001 (Box 160, Box 212)
  - Pintilie, Ileana, 1997-2001 (Box 160)
  - Piotrowski, Piotr, 1997 (Box 160)
  - Piper, Adrian, 2002 (Box 160)
  - Pistoletto, Michelangelo, 1999 (Box 160)
  - Poitras, Frederic, 1982 (Box 160)
  - Polansky, Rudolf, 2007-2008 (Box 160)
  - Pollock, Della (Box 160)
  - Pollock, Griselda, 1993-1994, 2012 (Box 160, Box 214)
  - Poonvoralak, Vichien (Box 160)
  - Popa-Liseanu, Doina, 1992 (Box 160)
  - Pope.L, William, 1999-2012 (Box 160)
  - Popovic, Zoran, 1995-2009 (Box 161)
  - Porges, Timo, 1990 (Box 161)
  - P-Orridge, Genesis, 1998 (Box 161)
  - Powell, Richard and C.T. Woods, 1990-2010, 2014 (Box 161, Box 214)
  - Pozzi, Lucio, 1988-2005 (Box 161)
  - Pratt, Vernon (Box 161)
  - Pratte, Marie Claude, 1998 (Box 161)
  - Preda-Sanc, Mariena, 1992-1996 (Box 161)
  - Presner, Todd Samuel, 2007 (Box 161)
  - Prestsaeter, Ellief, 2006 (Box 161)
  - Price, Mary Sue Sweeney, 1999 (Box 161)
  - Price, Lorna (Box 161)
  - Prince, Arnold, 1979 (Box 161)
  - Prince, Richard, 1999 (Box 161)
  - Princenthal, Nancy, 2010 (Box 161)
  - Printed Matter, Inc., 1999 (Box 161)
  - Prut, Constantin, 1997 (Box 161)
  - Quan, Roy, 1978 (Box 161)
  - Quiet Attentions: Departure from Women (Box 161)
  - Quinn, Nathaniel, 1995 (Box 161)
  - Quintero, Jhafis (Box 161)
  - Prisco, Rosemary, 1995 (Box 161)
  - Radway, Jean, 1998 (Box 161)
  - Rainer, Cosima, 2005 (Box 161)
  - Rainer, Yvonne (Box 161)
  - Rankin, Tom, 2011 (Box 161)
  - Rapoport, Sonja, 1997 (Box 161)
  - Rata, Vasile, 1998 (Box 161)
  - Raunch-o-Rama, 1994 (Box 161)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1997 (Box 161)
  - Reed, John W., 2001-2002 (Box 161)
  - Reed, Marcia, 2007 (Box 161)
  - Rees, Michael, 2003 (Box 161)
  - Regan, Tom, 2005 (Box 161)
  - Renda, Molly (Box 161)
  - Renn, Melissa, 2007 (Box 161)
  - Restany, Pierre, 1978-1989 (Box 161)
  - Reynolds, Jock, 2000 (Box 161)
  - Rhine Research Center, 1999 (Box 161)
  - Rice, Karen Gonzalez, 2010 (Box 161)
  - Richards, Catherine, 2000 (Box 161)
  - Richardson, Jeanne, 2009 (Box 161)
  - Richman, Lauren, 2010 (Box 161)
  - Rifkin, Ned, 1986 (Box 161)
  - Rinaldo, Kenneth E., 1997-1999 (Box 161)
  - Ringold, Faith, 1990 (Box 161)
  - Ritchey, David, 1998 (Box 161)
  - Ritcheym R.K., 1991 (Box 161)
  - Robertson, Clive, 2012 (Box 214)
  - Robbe-Grillet, Alain, 1977 (Box 161)
  - Roberson, Ruth, 1999 (Box 161)
  - Roberts, Liisa, 1999 (Box 161)
  - Robertson, Kendall, 2005 (Box 161)
  - Robinson, Cardeigh, 1995-2005 (Box 161)
  - Robinson, John (Box 162)
  - Rogula, Miroslaw, 1999 (Box 162)
  - Rogers, Kathleen (Box 162)
  - Rolleston, James, 1994-1997, 2013 and undated (Box 162, Box 214)
  - Roloff, John (Box 162)
  - Romanian Pavillion, Venice Biennale, 2007 (Box 162)
  - Romaschko, Sergej, 2000-2001 (Box 162)
  - Rorschach, Kim, 2008-2009, 2012 (Box 162, Box 214)
  - Rosen, Annabeth, 2000 (Box 162)
  - Rosen, James (Box 162)
  - Rosenquist, James, 2003 (Box 162)
  - Rosler, Martha, 1994-1996 (Box 162)
  - Rotando, Marina, 2012 (Box 214)
  - Ross, David, 1994-2009 (Box 162)
  - Roth, Moira, 1990-1997 (Box 162)
  - Roth, Nancy, 1999 (Box 162)
  - Roth, Susan, 2007 (Box 162)
  - Rothfuss, Joan, 2004 (Box 162)
  - Rothschild, Gail, 1992-1993 (Box 162)
  - Rotterdam, Paul, 1984-1985 (Box 162)
  - Routh, Mitali, 2007 (Box 162)
  - Royal Academy Ghent, Belgium: Stiles' talk, 2011 (Box 162)
  - Royes, Victor A. and Catherine, 1985-1994 (Box 162)
  - Rozene, Janette, 1980-1983 (Box 162)
  - Rozzelle, Ron and Patton, Rosa Ragan, 1997-2005, 2013-2014 (Box 162, Box 214)
  - Rubell, Jason (Box 162)
  - Rubins, Nancy, 2006, 2014 (Box 162, Box 214)
  - Rudy, Kathy, 2007, 2012 (Box 162, Box 214)
  - Ruhe, Harry, 1992-2000 (Box 162)
  - Ruller, Tomas (Box 162)
    - Russell, Clark, 1983 (Box 214)
  - Rusu, Olga, 1998 (Box 162)
  - Ruta, Laurentiu (Box 163)
  - Saglova, Zorka, 2000 (Box 163)
  - Sala, Anri (Box 163)
  - Saltzman, Marvin, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Saltzman, Lisa, 2004 (Box 163)
  - Salvo, Calogero, 1984-1989 (Box 163)
  - San Francisco Art Institute, 2001 (Box 163)
  - San Francisco Camerawork (Frish Brandt) (Box 163)
  - Sanchez, Marc, 1982 (Box 163)
  - Sandor, Antik, 1994 (Box 163)
  - Sanyal, Sunanda, 2007-2009 (Box 163)
  - Saper, Craig, 2001 (Box 163)
  - Saunter, Chris, 1999 (Box 163)
  - Sava, Sharla, 1993 (Box 163)
  - Savic, Miroslav Misa, Vienna, 1979 (Box 163)
  - Sayre, Henry, 1995 (Box 163)
  - Scarritt, Alan, 1994 (Box 163)
  - Schapina, Sarit (Box 163)
  - Schellack, Christine, 2006 (Box 163)
  - Scherlippens, Bjorn, 2011 (Box 163)
  - Schimmel, Paul, 1994-1999 (Box 163)
  - Schllock, Jessica, 2002 (Box 163)
  - Schmidt, Lynn (Box 163)
  - Schneemann, Carolee, 2003-2009, 2012-2013 (Box 163)
  - Schneider, Rebecca, 2002 (Box 163)
  - Schor, Mira, 1990 (Box 163)
  - Schorr, Collier, 1999 (Box 163)
  - Schreib, Werner, 1967 (Box 163)
  - Schroeder, Johannes L., 1984 (Box 163)
  - Schwartz, Arturo, 1978-1983 (Box 163)
  - Schwartzenberg, Susan, 1998 (Box 164)
  - Scott, Jill (Box 164)
  - Seagull, Sara, 2001 (Box 164)
  - Sei, Keiko (Box 164)
  - Selz, Peter, 1997-2009 (Box 164)
  - Selz, Gabriella, 1982 (Box 164)
  - Semah, Joseph, 1991 (Box 164)
  - Serebrennikov, Nina, 1997 (Box 164)
  - Sester, Marie, 2007 (Box 164)
  - Sex and Space, 1996 (Box 164)
  - Shafir, Wendy, 1997-2001 (Box 164)
  - Shambroom, Paul, 1989-2006 (Box 164)
  - Shannon, Joe, 1998 (Box 164)
  - Sharp, M.J., 2007 (Box 164)
  - Sharp, Willoughby, 1999-2008 (Box 164)
  - Shaw, Jeffrey, 1985 (Box 164)
  - Sheldon, April (Box 164)
  - Shevk, Bonnie, 2009 (Box 164)
  - Sherry, Jane (Box 164)
  - Shiff, Richard, 1986-2003 (Box 164)
  - Shimamoto, Shozo, 1999 (Box 164)
  - Shin, Jeong Ah (Box 164)
  - Sibio, Linda, 2003 (Box 164)
  - Sichel, Berta, 1998 (Box 164)
  - Siefert-Rose, Joan (Box 164)
  - Siemans Art Program (Box 164)
  - Sigmund Martin Heller Travelling Fellowship (Box 164)
  - Signer, Roman, 1998 (Box 164)
  - Sikorski, Rob, 2002-2009 (Box 164)
  - Silbiger, Alexander (Box 164)
  - Silk, Suzanne Royce, 1998 (Box 164)
  - Silverman, Gilbert, 2001 (Box 164)
  - Simbula, Massimiliano, 2008 (Box 164)
  - Simionescu, Doina, 1996 (Box 164)
  - Simon, Anna, 2010 (Box 164)
  - Simon, Peggy, 1984-1990 (Box 164)
  - Skinner, Sally, 1997 (Box 164)
  - Smash Lab and Messer, Chuck (Box 196)
  - Smith, Barbara, 1998-2006 (Box 196)
  - Smith, Dean, 1985-2009 (Box 196)
  - Smith, Kim, 2000 (Box 196)
  - Smith Owen, 1990-1996 (Box 196)
  - Smith, Terence, 2008 (Box 196)
  - Smith, W. Eugene and Kevin Eugene, 2008 (Box 196)
  - Smolinsky, Susan, 1998 (Box 196)
  - Snow, Lila, 1998-2002 (Box 196)
  - Soeharto, Tien, 1993 (Box 196)
  - Sohm, Hanns, 1980-1997 (Box 196)
  - Solnit, Rebecca (Box 196)
  - Solow, David, 2007 (Box 196)
  - Son, Jah King, 2000 (Box 196)
  - Sonfist, Alan, 2005-2009 (Box 196)
  - Sontag, David, 2005 (Box 196)
  - Soros Center for Contemporary Art (Box 196)
  - Spector, Buzz, 2011 (Box 196)
  - Spataru, Mircea, 1992-1993 (Box 196)
  - Spoerri, Daniel, 2000 (Box 196)
  - Sprinkle, Annie M. (Box 196)
  - Stachelberg, Cas, 1994 (Box 196)
  - Stafford, Barbara (Box 196)
  - Stahl, Harvey, 1984 (Box 196)
  - Stairs, David C., 2007 (Box 196)
  - Stanciulescu, Serban, 1978 (Box 196)
  - Stanescu, Mircea, 1993-1997 (Box 196)
  - Stanculescu, Eugen (Box 196)
  - Starr, Adam (Box 196)
  - Stein, Judith E. (Box 196)
  - Stein-Barrett, Tzivia, 1983 (Box 196)
  - Steinheider, Brigitte, 2002 (Box 196)
  - Steirischer herbst (Box 197, Box 214)
  - STELARC, 1984-1990 (Box 197)
  - Sterbak, Jana, 1999 (Box 197)
  - Stevens, Cici, 1991 (Box 197)
  - Stevens, Graham, 1987-1989 (Box 197)
  - Stiehm, Judith Hicks (Box 197)
  - Stih, Renate, 1990 (Box 197)
  - Stitt, Andre, 1999-2003 (Box 197)
  - Stone, Alan, 1993-2000 (Box 197)
  - Stone-Richards, Michael (Box 197)
  - Stout, Renee, 2000 (Box 198)
  - Strauss, David Levi (Box 198)
  - Stromfeldt, Mette, 1995 (Box 198)
  - Student Cultural Center, Belgrade (Box 198)
  - Students (Box 198)
  - Subrin, Elisabeth (Box 198)
  - SubRosa, 2007 (Box 198)
  - Sudek, Josef, 2009 (Box 198)
  - Sugar, Janos (Box 198)
  - Summer Academy Lectures, 2010 (Box 198)
  - Summers, David, 1998 (Box 198)
  - Summers, Dennis, 2004 (Box 198)
  - Surin, Kenneth, 2007 (Box 198)
  - Survival Research Laboratories, Pauline, Mark (Box 198)
  - Sykes, Michael, 1977 (Box 198)
  - Szymanski, Carol (Box 198)
  - Tan, Tai Young, 2008 (Box 198)
  - Takemoto, Tina, 2002 (Box 198)
  - Tap International (Box 198)
  - Tapies, Antoni, 1995 (Box 198)
  - Tarantino, Christine, 2010-2013 (Box 198)
  - Tatro, Kelley, 2004 (Box 198)
  - Taylor, Marvin, 2003 (Box 198)
  - Taylor, Russell, 1997 (Box 198)
  - Tenney, James, 2001 (Box 198)
  - Theater Fletch Bizzel-Team (Box 198)
  - Tetel Andresen, Julie, 1997-2014 (Box 198)
  - Thomas, Lew, 1979 (Box 198)
  - Thomas, Michael J. (Box 198)
  - Thompson, Mark, 1974-1976, 1980s, 2014 and undated (Box 198)
  - Thompson, Robert J., 2006-2007 (Box 198)
  - Thompson, Rosie, 1991-1993 (Box 198)
  - Thun-Hohenstein, Christoph, 2002 (Box 199)
  - Timisoara, 1990-1992 (Box 199)
  - Timotijevic, Slavko, 1978 (Box 199)
  - Tiney, Alexander, 1996 (Box 199)
  - Tinguely, Jean, 2003 (Box 199)
  - Tiryakian, Jocefina, 2004 (Box 199)
  - Titu, Alexandra (Box 199)
  - Tolan, Vasile (Box 199)
  - Tomas, David, 1997-1999 (Box 199)
  - Tomii, Raiko, 2005 (Box 199)
  - Tomkins, Calvin, 1978 (Box 199)
  - Toncian, Titu (Box 199)
  - Tost, Tony, 2006 (Box 199)
  - Touchton, Judith, 1991 (Box 199)
  - Transit-hu, 2006 (Box 199)
  - Tsong-Zung Johnson, Chang, 2000 (Box 199)
  - Tudor, David, 2001 (Box 199)
  - Tumbas, Jasmina, 2009-2014 (Box 199)
  - Turner, Paula, 2004 (Box 212)
  - Tweel, Tamara Mann (Box 199)
  - Typographic Society (Box 199)
  - Ulay (Laysiepen, Uwe), 2013 (Box 214)
  - Umbrella, 1991 (Box 199)
  - "Under the Big Back Sun: California Art, 1974-1981" Museum of Contemporary Art, 2010 (Box 199)
  - Unica T (Box 199)
  - University of California Press (Box 199)
  - University of Indiana, Robert and Avis Burke Lecture Series (Box 199)
  - Ursprung, Philip, 2000-2001 (Box 199)
  - Uto, Gusztav (Box 199)
  - V2 Organisatie, 1990-1996 (Box 199)
  - Vagle, Gwen, 2000 (Box 199)
  - Vale, V. and Juno, Andrea, 1992 (Box 199)
  - Van Abbe Museum, 2012-2013 (Box 214)